Oh, don't be surprised.
え、ひょわれたなよ
Hello.
こんにちは
What's wrong with you, you're so close?
どうしたの、そんなにくっついて、
Both of us.
2人とも
We're good friends.
仲いいんで
Are you good friends?
仲いいの?
We're good friends.
仲いいんで
friend?
友達?
that's right.
そうです
Can I come in too?
俺も入っていい?
Inside, in the middle.
中、真ん中
A little in the middle.
真ん中ちょっと
Because it rang, now.
鳴らされたからさ、今
got it.
わかりました
That's fine then.
じゃあいいですよ
Wow, something like this...
うわ、なんか、こんな...
picture?
え?
Such luxury...
こんな贅沢な...
Eh, hey, something, today, something...
え、ちょ、なんかさ、 今日、なんか、
Do something fun with the two of us.
2人と、 なんか、楽しいことをね、
That person told me I could do it, but
していいって、あの人に言われたんだけど、
Are you listening?
聞いてる?
I haven't heard it.
聞いてないです
I don't know.
知らないです
i don't know?
知らない?
Huh, what kind of relationship do you two have?
え、2人は、どういう関係なの?
We are friends.
友達です
Are you friends?
友達なの?
How many friends?
何友だろう?
We're from the same university.
同じ大学の子ね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I'm 20.
私が20です
20?
It's 19.
19です
Seriously?
マジ?
I like it, like this.
いいね、こんな形
A man close to 30.
30近い男が
They're both so cute, though.
すげえ可愛いんだけど、2人とも
From now on, it's like, with the two of us as opponents,
今から、なんか、 俺2人を相手に、
Have you ever done something like that?
そういうのは、したことある?
3P-like.
3P的な
No.
ないです
There isn't.
ないんだ
Let's compare the smells.
匂い比べしようかな
Compare the smells.
匂い比べ
It smells good.
いい匂いする
Both smell different.
どっちも違う匂いするね
Is it okay to do something so extravagant?
こんな贅沢なことしちゃっていいの?
Are you using Malm shampoo?
マルムシャンプー使ってる?
picture?
え?
It's lemon.
レモンだね
Really, lemons and roses.
本当に、 レモンとバラ
I think I'll try one of them for a moment.
ちょっと、どっちかチューしようかな
Is there anyone who wants to play with me?
俺とチューしたい子いる?
If you want to play with me, please raise your hand.
俺とチューしたい子、 手あげてごらん?
Hey!
おい!
Do you want to play with me?
俺とチューしたいの?
Hey!
おい!
We both stuck out our tongues,
2人で舌を出して、
Have you ever done something like this?
こんな ことしたことある?
do not have?
ない?
So, how about we both have a bite?
じゃあ、2人でさ、 チューしてごらん?
Have you two ever been with a girl?
2人は女の子としたことある?
first time?
初めて?
Would you like to fill it up?
いっぱいしてごらん?
Stick out your tongue and slurp.
舌を出して、ベロベロ
Can you stick your tongue out?
舌を出してごらん?
Then touch my butt.
それでお尻触って
They both have nice feet.
2人ともきれいな足してるね
Very much.
すごく
Eh, what is this?
え、なにこれ?
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
this.
これ
It's so see-through.
スケスケだよ
You can't see my panties, me.
パンツ見えないじゃん、俺
I can't see you, pants.
見えないよ、パンツ
Both of them are amazing.
2人ともすごい
Super beautiful.
超きれい
They're both breathing really well.
2人とも すっごいいい息をしてるね、
Both of us.
2人とも
They're both great.
2人とも最高だよ
Can we both sit together?
2人で座れないか
The two of us get along well.
2人で仲良く
You have really nice legs
すごいきれいな足してる
hey.
ね
Have you seen it?
見 たことある?
What does this friend look like?
この友達のこんな姿は
do not have?
ない?
How do you feel?
どんな気分?
Is this a sketch pen?
こんなスケペンなの?
Both of you, stand up for a moment.
ちょっと2人ともさ、立って
One person wants to see it.
1人が見たくなる
Not a bit.
ちょっとないじゃん
Have you ever seen them naked?
2人の裸見たことあるの?
do not have.
ない
Like a lecture room.
講演室とかね
So beautiful.
すごいきれい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's so beautiful.
すごいきれいじゃん
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
The style is also amazing.
スタイルもすごい
I really like the style, both of you.
超スタイルいいね、2人とも
Looks like a model.
モデルみたいじゃん
Are you doing something?
何かやってる?
Model?
モデル?
I haven't done it.
やってない
copper?
どう?
first time?
初めて?
first time
初めて
Right?
で しょ?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
soft.
柔らかい
What about this?
こっちは?
soft.
柔らかい
Why do you hide it?
なんで隠すの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Let me show you.
見せてあげよう
Let me take a look.
見てあげて
So beautiful.
すごいきれい
You touched it.
触ってあげたじゃん
Yeah.
うん
Both of us were licked.
2人で舐められた
Does this feel good?
こっちは気持ちいい?
right and left.
右と左
Let me lick it.
舐めてあげよう
amazing.
すごい
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
amazing.
すごい
what?
何?
Let's sit down.
座ってみよう
It's really soft.
すごい柔らかいね
soft.
柔らかい
Why are you trying to take a picture of me?
なんで俺の副面撮ろうとしてるの?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
right and left.
右と左
left.
左
left?
左?
Is it better to be friends?
友達のほうがいいの?
Yeah.
うん
That's amazing, both of you.
すごいね、2人とも
Turn your butt over there because it's a snack.
お尻をあっちに向けて、 おつまみになったから
We both shook our butts.
2人でお尻をふりふりして
amazing.
すごい
Both of them are erotic.
2人ともエロい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
How many faces do they both have at the same time?
2人とも、 同時に、 何個の顔?
Let's take a look.
見てみよう
Both are beautiful.
どっちも綺麗だね
It's blue.
青いね
Both are delicious.
どっちもおいしくね
Want to exchange sounds at home?
家に音交換しとく?
Sound exchange at home.
家に音交換
So sexy.
すごいセクシー
This one is also narrow.
こっちも狭いね
Can two people sit?
2人で座れる?
amazing.
すごい
It's a beautiful body.
綺麗な体だね
Let's give it a try with two people.
足2人であげてみようか
Looks like we're both going to pee together.
2人でおしっこせみたいだね
Spread it out, how many pieces?
広げてごらん、何個
How many of mine?
自分の何個
Amazing, just the two of us.
すごい、2人で
It's delicious, amazing.
おいしいね、すごい
The distance has gotten shorter.
距離が縮まったね